A look to kill for.
The Stylist is a horror, drama film directed by Jill Gevargizian.
Claire is a lonely hairstylist who secretly murders and scalps her clients.
When Olivia makes the well-intentioned mistake of asking Claire to style her hair for her wedding, she
becomes dangerously obsessed, and her sanity starts to slip away with bloody consequences.
Claire, played by Najarra Townsend.
Olivia, played by Brea Grant.
Frankie, played by Laura Kirk.
Monique, played by Millie Milan.
Rose, played by Kimberly Igla.
Minister, played by Kyle Ament.
The Stylist is a 2020 American horror drama film produced,
co-written and directed by Jill Gevargizian.
The film is based on the director's short film of the same
name and stars Najarra Townsend and Brea Grant.
The film premiered at the 2020 Fantastic Fest.
The tone is dark and emotional.